"Having settled me in the wedding
palanquin the bearer"
"carried me on behalf of my beloved"
"Having settled me in the
wedding palanquin"
"I passed a few days of joy...."
"....for a thousand days of sorrow"
"Having settled me in the wedding palanquin"
"Dying I had to emerge"
"Dying I had to emerge
living I had to depart...."
"....my beloved's house"
"Blisters formed on feet like flowers"
"when they had to walk on thorns"
"Its autumn, its autumn"
"Having settled me in the wedding palanquin"
"As many tears in my eyes
there isnt that...."
"......much water in the river"
"Such were the things you wrote to me"
".....they seemed to shatter my fate"
"Done with intermediaries
the debt between us was dismissed"
"Having settled me in the wedding palanquin"
Lakhaniya, Take Nandu inside!
Ram!
Such a small child lost his mother!
God has been unjust to you!
Whose it?
Pushpa!
Are you coming from your in laws place?
Yes
Spoiled face...
.....upset!
Definately something is wrong!
Uncle who is she?
You remember Damodar Dayaal?
Who liked chanting!
Yes
She is his daughter!
Mother
Pushpa what brought you here?
Mother!
What happen?
Why are you crying?
Have you fought and come?
I will never return back again
I will stay here
With you
Have you lost it?
Atleast say what happen?
I couldnt conceive...
So he married another girl!
What?
Yes mother
I tolerated this!
I kept tolerating their torture!
Still you shouldnt have left
your house!
A husband's house is a woman's
world for her!
I wanted to die there!
But I was helpless and so
I have come here
I dont accept this!
Even you must be at fault!
My fault was....
......I lived there inspite of
this torture!
But today...
...see this!
They hit me with a burning stick!
And then they pushed me out
of the house!
My child!
If you also dont support me...
....where else will I go?
I'm living with the help of others
How will I feed you?
Dont you worry mother!
I'll beg!
I'll find a job from somewhere!
But dont ask me to return back!
Dont ask me to return back
Dont cry!
Dont cry
Come inside!
C'mon
Mahesh, this time your wedding should be a grand one!
What are you saying!
If Nandu was not a child.....
.....I wouldnt have got
married for the second time
That is there
But
Pushpa was at your place?
Its a wrong decision!
Why did she come to your place?
To ask for a job!
For a job?
-Yes
I know her in laws
very well!
Belongs to a gluttonous family!
Definitely there's a problem!
Must be, I havent asked!
Anyway, forget that!
Tell me one thing...
.....when has the auspicious date for wedding
been fixed?
On the 24th of this month!
Very good, quickly got engaged followed by immediate
wedding!
Look dont worry about anything!
I'll make all the arangements!
Okay I am leaving
Pushpa!
You are shy?
You sat on my lap when
in your childhood!
Again I went wrong!
You played on my lap in your childhood!
You remember?
Then how can you forget me?
Why did you go to Mahesh's
place to ask for job?
When mahesh told me about this
I was very upset!
I wouldnt like inspite of me
being present...
.....any problems come to you or
your mother!
I'll give you work!
You?
Yes!
I have a big business in Calcutta!
I have land, and a house!
But no one to look after it!
Whenever I go there!
I swipe the floor!
I prepare my food!
If you take care of all that...
.....you benefit yourself!
And will even benefit myself!
But, uncle... I!
I am talking for your good!
In Calcutta is there a shoratge
of servants?
No
My mother is old....
...how can I leave her alone and go?
Yes you have to think about it!
I am in no hurry!
You think and give me an answer!
I give you a job there!
Okay
I'll think about it and let
you know!
You?
What is it?
Manjula Bhabhi, can I borrow some
rice from you?
Borrow?
Why dont you say you.....
....have come to beg!
Okay think like you
are giving me alms!
I am not asking for myself!
I'll stay hungry!
But my mother!
Go away from here!
Arent you ashamed of leaving
your husband and begging everywhere!
Its a sin seeing you!
Go!
Pushpa!
You went to my place, right?
Sister in law, insulted you and
removed you, right?
No
The one who has no respect,
an insult doesnt matter!
Dont say this Pushpa
Take this keep the money!
But
Keep it!
Keep it
The help you have given me...
Forget that, you should
help one another!
I have helped you and you...!
What do you mean?
No one is there on the other
side of lake in the evenings!
Arent you ashamed?
You are like my brother!
By giving me money you want
to buy me?
Did you see it?
-Yes mother!
Uncle caught her hand and
gave her money!
Really?
Come along with me!
But what happen?
Atleast tell me!
Your daughter has coaxed my
brother in law and has taken money from him
He has seen it
Ask!
Dint you see?
Yes I saw
Arent you contented with begging?
That you called your daughter
to coax others?
Bitch
Shut up
Shut up sister in law
We are not bitches...
....your brother in law is a scoundrel!
What?
Shut up
Bitch!
Shamless
How much did you take
from her brother in law?
And why did you take?
Mother
Dare if you call me mother
Why dint I die before hearing...
....what all she said because of you!
Mother atleast listen to me!
Go away from here!
You are an Unchaste woman
and so your husband has thrown you out!
Go and drown yourself somewhere!
How dare you insult my brother in law!
Pushpa, what are you doing?
You are going to commit suicide?
Very bad, get up!
Had I passed away?
Its sheer disgrace, inspite of me being there
you face problems!
Come right now!
Come to Calcutta!
So many times have we asked
you girls to watch movies!
They dont like folk songs!
People like songs of movies!
None of you like working!
Aunty Greetings!
Greetings!
Nepal Babu, you have come here after
so long, welcome!
I had gone to the village!
Come Pushpa
Come
Who is she?
Pushpa
She is from our village!
She is
Sad! Come child
Go
Dont get scared
Aunt has started this Hermitage for
girls like you!
Yes child
Girls learn to sing and
dance here!
Do you know how to sing?
She has a very sweet voice!
Her father was a well known singer
Really?
He has only trained her!
Let the master come...
...only he can test her voice!
Okay aunty when should I come?
Come after a week!
Okay I am leaving
I'll have to stay here uncle?
Yes
Consider her like your mother...
....if you listen to her and
keep her happy....
...then you'll be more than happy!
Yes aunty?
Okay
Dont worry I'll visit you often!
Aunty take her away!
Come child, feel homely!
Welcome Sir, you are coming
here after a long time!
Babuji, Should I take you to the
real charm of this lane?
To Munni!
C'mon!
Go away
Cant you see he is educated!
Take someone else!
Babuji, come!
You must have heard Krishna's name!
C'mon!
Dont touch me!
You have got me to this dirty place?
Babuji, if a travellor tells me to take him
anywhere at this hour...
...I ought to get him here!
Lets go back
"The night is passing but Krishna does not come..."
"I get no sleep"
"The night is passing"
Anand Babu
Welcome Anand Babu, you and
here?
Dint you recognize me?
Please sing
Why did you stop?
Sing
"Krishna forgot his promise..."
"Radha sits with her lamp, in wait for him."
"I get no sleep"
"The night is passing but Krishna does not come..."
"The night is passing"
"The blow of the lament makes the lover mad..."
"The heart and body are thirsty;
tears in the eyes."
"I get no sleep"
"The night is passing but Krishna does not come..."
"The night is passing"
You turned this room
into a temple!
Whoever you are, your voice can
take a man's pain away from him!
You heard that?
He praised her so well!
Do you know who is he?
He is one of the those wealthy people
of the city!
I have old relations
with him!
Really? She is really fortuitous!
She sang for the first time and
Anand Babu came here!
I havent come....
....the magic in her voice pulled
me here!
Keep visiting us everyday, Anand Babu!
Pushpa's house is your house!
Your name is Pushpa?
Should have been Meera!
Please have this!
Mahesh brother will forget his first
wife seeing your red lips!
Oh child...
Go to your new mother!
Come!
Nandu, come here quickly
Nalu, look at this nest!
I'll place it on a branch!
Why will you place it
on a branch?
On a full moon day, a bird's mother will
keep 3 eggs in it...
....and we'll play with her kids!
On a full moon day?
-Yes
I wont be here till then!
-Why?
Where are you going?
Calcutta! My new mother has
said now we'll stay there!
You'll wont come back to the village?
No, my father is seeing a place!
As and when we get a place
we all will shift there!
The house is good
But if you could compromise
a bit on the rent?
I am sorry!
This same house in some area would
have double rent!
You are also getting ready
furniture!
As you wish
When are you all coming?
On the 1st!
Advance of 2 months!
Yes, why not
Take this
Thank you, and even your receipt is ready!
OkaY Greetings!
Greetings!
Mahesh Brother!
You?
Did not recognize me?
I am Pushpa
Who Pushpa?
Excellent, you have forgotten me?
You forgot your sister?
Remember I had asked you for
a job once?
I recollected!
But what are you doing?
Come inside!
You'll get wet in the rains!
no, I am in a hurry!
Let rains stop
Come
Come in
Everybody is fine at home?
Yes
Your son Nandu?
He must have grown till now?
Yes
Sit
I'll just come!
You are still standing?
Sit
Have this sweet!
No, I wont have anything!
How is that possible?
I have met you after so long...
...I cant go without serving!
No, No Pushpa
I am getting late!
The rains have reduced
I have to catch the evening train!
You are going back to
the village?
Yes
Wait for a minute
Please give 50 rupees to my mother!
To your mother?
Yes
I am really worried about her
So whenever possible...
....I keep sending her things!
Whom do you send it with?
Through Nepal babu...
....because of him I am here today!
I keep sending things through
him!
I cant face anyone from the village!
Take this and give it to my
mother!
Take this!
You keep the money
Pushpa
Sorry, I think I have come on
a wrong time!
No, he is my brother!
from my village!
Mahesh Brother!
Sorry but seeing money...
....I was mistakened!
This is Pushpa's money
I was sending it for my mother!
Yes I remember....
...very often you send
money to your mother!
Keep them
Now dont send it!
Why?
Because your mother has passed away!
What?
No one informed me!
Pushpa, you have expired for the villagers!
Who'll inform you if you
dont exist for them!
Okay I am leaving
Greetings
Dont cry Pushpa...
....whatever you are and wherever you are...
....your tears are just like saline water
Wipe them Pushpa
I hate tears
Yes
You are right Anand Babu!
You are right!
Sit
Take this!
Let it be
Lets go out somewhere
Where?
Some place...
...just for sometime...
....no thoughts creep in my mind!
Neither you nor me!
"If a spark flares up"
"If a spark flares up, then the rains might extinguish it"
"...but if the rains light a fire, who can put it out?"
"who can put it out?"
"If the autumn lays waste to a garden..."
"....the spring will bring that garden into flower"
"But if that garden is destroyed in the springtime"
"who can make it bloom?"
"Don't ask me how the temple of dreams shattered"
"it is not a matter of people,
this is a story for intimates."
"If some enemy strikes you a blow"
"your friend will cheer your heart"
"but if a loved one inflicts the wound"
"who will erase it?"
"Who knows what would happen,
who knows what we would do."
"If we drink then we live; if we dont drink, we die"
"If the world thirsts"
"then wine will quench it"
"But if the wine thirsts"
"who can satisfy its need"
"who can satisfy its need?"
"I understand that in the face of a storm,
no one's force will work."
"But this isn't the fault of the waves"
"someone else is to blame"
"If in midstream a boat rocks"
"then the sailor can cast it ashore"
"But if the sailor sinks it midstream"
"who can save it?"
"A spark"
My son will become fair
He'll become very fair
Put it
Kamla, I am going to the market
to get some stuffs
Remove my clothes and keep
Once I come will immediately
go to the office
Okay
Father, even I want to come along with you!
No, you have to go to the school!
Take him along, he'll see the shop
and if I want something he'll get it!
Eat son!
C'mon!
My sweet child!
Pushpa, last night you were fighting
with your Babu?
What for?
He was drunk....
...so I had to forcibly send
him home!
Aunty, welcome!
Surprising!
What else can he do besides
fighting with you!
Sometimes he even does
that!
Whatever it is, whether you feel
good or bad!
If you upset him, you'll suffer
for the rest of your life!
Dont give me a lecture
in mornings!
Take this!
Your commision!
Your are very sweet!
I never have to tell you
anything for money?
So girls....
...there was a lot of noise
coming from your houses!
We have kept your money...
...come and take it!
Lets go
Oh ho Did you see that?
They behave like I beg in front of them!
They waste money on cosmetics...
...and when they have to give me money
its
I'll just go and ask them!
Our house is here!
Nandu, dont run you'll
fall!
Hey!
You called me?
Yes, who stay here?
You bought that empty flat?
Lets go father!
Is he Nandu?
He has grown so big
I had seen him when he was a child!
Nandu take this bag and go home!
I am just coming
He has grown old
Look Pushpa!
Dont talk to me after today
Why brother?
Because the area you stay in...
.....is not acceptable by the society!
And I stay in the society
I can be defamed if I talk to you
or meet you!
So I dont want anyone to know
that we know each other
What is it?
Why are you peeping in?
Naughty, its you?
Nandu, listen to me!
Open the door!
Shankar,what happen?
She is not opening the door
What happen?
What is this noise for?
Something happened!
-What happen?
Shankar is stading with a knife
outside Durga's room!
And she is not opening the door
And where is aunty?
Aunty has gone out somewhere
with her father
Shankar is drunk he might
kill her!
7 murders are excused in that state!
Lets see!-No
I wont let you go there
Shankar is a very dangerous man
Sometimes you have to take risks in life!
There is no spice left otherwise
Lets go
Red eyes, with a knife in your hand and
poses like Lord Shiva
How did you come here?
What?
Just give me this knife
Atleast give it to me!
This is so small!
Where is your spearhead?
What nonsense are you talking?
Dint understand?
No
Your name is Shankar
and you are innocent
.....and you have misunderstood this Concubinary
as your wife....
...who'll come running and will open the door!
Now you tell me how would you taste
any syrup while drinking beer!
What are you saying?
Durga
Open the door Durga
Anand Babu has come here
Dont get scared
Not at all
Is anyone there inside?
Then why werent you opening the door?
My child is suffering from fever...
...he wasnt leaving me!
Babuji, have mercy on me and
please ask him to leave!
Understood
Understood!
That bitch closed the door?
Inspite of hearing this you are still high?
This child that is suffering from fever
is your child?
Mine?
No!
I am not his father
Durga belongs to you then who so ever
may be the father!
Yes thats there!
Her child also belongs to you!
Yes
If you love her go and call a doctor,
her child is not keeping well!
Doctor?
Durga is not well?
I'll just go and get a doctor!
Shankarji!-Yes!
Take your bribe!
Durga is not keeping well!
The fight is over!
Pushpa...
...will I get little?
I was scared, if something
would have happened to you!
What has to happen will
happen!
Every man should get a chance
to show his qualities!
Dint you see how I became
a hero outside?
All the fun has died, just prepare
one more glass!
Pushpa
Anand Babu!
Greetings!
I am sorry, I came at a wrong time!
Dont feel bad
What are you saying gentleman?
What inopportune time for you?
You are the owner
Afterall you have done this good job
of getting this decent girl here!
Had you not been there...
....who would blossom this flower
in this garden!
Anand babu, you are embarrassing me
Really?
I wont wait for a longer time!
Pushpa, I am going to the village
tomorrow!
Your mother had asked for more
50 rupees last time!
My Mother?
Nepal Babu
Yes
Sometimes even a cow raises its head
while eating grass!
May be to thank god!
But I dont think
you would ever raise your head, Isnt it?
The one who sits above us...
....arent you scared of him?
I dint understand anything!
You did not understand?
C'mon outside!
I'll explain you!
Pushpa knows...
What does she know?
Everyone staying here also know it!
What?
That her mother has passed away!
So drop the curtains...
....the show is over!
Where are you off to Nepal Babu?
Take it!
No
Take it gentleman
All this time you had no shame
then why today?
Till you are alive live a life
this way!
Leave Nepal Babu!
Go
Hey Nandu
Are you coming from the school?
-Yes
My New mother!
What is it?
Give me good!
After sometime!
I am very hungry...
....new mother
I told you come after sometime!
Wont you take a bath, brother?
Yes, go and take a bath first
I'll take a bath in the lake opposite
our house!
Go wherever you want and
dont eat my head! Go!
Mother I am hungry!
I'll serve you right now!
Come to me
You are hungry?
New mother, I took a bath...
...now please serve me!
Cant you see I am boiling clothes!
Cant you wait?
Give me anything to eat
I am very hungry!
I'll slap you, I asked you to wait for
sometime, are you going from here?
Is my darling son more hungry?
Yes son?
Take this! Eat it!
What happen?
What did you break?
How did this break?
Give me an answer
Say
Give me an answer!
Why are you quite?
You learnt to steal now?
What are you looking at me,
get down!
Punk, scoundrel, cheeky!
You have started stealing
I'll hit you if you again step
in this room!
Go away from here!
Nandu, why are you sitting here?
Its so late, wont you
go home?
No, my new mother hits me!
Why?
I broke the bottle of pickles!
I was very hungry
You havent eaten food as yet?
Dont cry
Eat
Sweet
Eat your mouth
Now whenever you are hungry
come to me
Will you come?
But dont tell anybody
And now dont cry
A good boy never cries
Say
Eat
Nandu!
Excellent
Your dress is very nice!
Your father got it for you?
Yes
Whom are these Samosa (fried or baked pastry) made for?
-No
Dont touch it!
Say
They are stale ones!
I love Samosa (fried or baked pastry)
Really?
I'll get hot Samosa (fried or baked pastry) for you
tommorow
Have a sweet today
Take this!
Take some more!
Now you go!
Why?
What why?
It is going to be evening!
Go home and study
I do all that in the evening
And I play in the evening!
Still you leave
Some guests are coming....
....you shouldnt be here!
Why?
What will they do?
Nothing
I am asking you to go,
so please go
Who are those guests?
Your brother?
You wont understand all that!
Go, and come soon tomorrow!
I'll get many Samosa (fried or baked pastry) for you!
Go
Today's day was very bad!
Not even a single work done!
No, Work was done...
..atleast I came to know the man who
just left from here was a scoundrel!
Exactly he is a rascal!
Anyway leave all that...
...ask my sister in law to make
tea
Anita!
Sir, madam is not at home!
No problem, please make
2 cups of tea for us!
Okay
Vijay, you sit I'll change
and come!
Okay
Listen
Leave the cigarette here!
Sure!
What is all this?
Our servant cant see all this?
He doesnt do anything
Balraam!
You called me Sir?
What is all this?
Pick it up!
And when I call you,
why dont you answer to me?
How do I answer when my name is Hariraam
and you call Balraam!
Yes I forgot!
Hariraam ji!
Balraam was your elder brother!
He was a very nice man!
He was a strong man and people
were scared of him!
And when evening falls he had a habit
of drinking just like me!
Understood Balraam?
Its Hariraam Sir!
Oh yes sorry!
Hariraam ji!
I want to change my clothes!
Can you get my pyjama?
Yes I'll just get it!
Where are my slippers?
Hariraam
Your pyjama is wet!
Its wet, it has still
not dried up!
I only have 1 pair of pyjamas?
Rest all are in the cupboard
and its locked
The keys are with madam
Give me one loincloth!
Okay
Sir I am not getting your loincloth
I am tired of finding one!
What are you saying Hariram?
You had suplied unlimited number
of saris...
....during stealing clothes of draupadi!
...and not even a single loincloth for me?
Very bad
Must have gone for a wash!
Okay make tea...
...and then go to the laundry
and get my clothes!
Okay
You havent still changed your clothes?
Do you know when do you
change the cover?
When People love the book!
New editions are published!
But in this house...
....the book named 'Me' has become old!
Neither anyone wants to look at it...
...nor anyone likes it!
Sir
Its difficult to make tea!
Why?
The milk has spoiled!
Stitch it!
Sorry?
How will you stitch milk?
Do you know where has she gone?
Yes she has gone to a saloon!
For hair dressing!
To the saloon for hair dressing?
Go....
....and get 2 cups of tea
from the restuarant opposite us!
No, let it be
Come with me to my house!
Asi is there!
You know what will you get along with tea?
Puri with a vegetable of potato and
hot Pudding!
My wife dresses her hair
at home!
She dresses at home?
-Yes
Look at me!
I have a house and a wife
that's equal to not having!
Anand, can I tell you something?
Dont feel bad
You are only responsible for this
However your wife must be....
....she will never want her husband to
spend a night somewhere else!
Vijay, a man works like a machine
all day...
...but when he comes back home
he wants something!
And when he doesnt get that at home!
He searches for it outside
Hello, whose this?
Madam?
Yes Sir has come
Sir, its madam on the phone!
Let it be?
Okay!
Okay
Sir, madam had called
She'll attend a party after leaving
from the saloon
She'll come home late
in the night!
Did you see that?
Its not just my habit to
come home late...
Forget it
You wont understand!
I told you...
Go home!
Wont you come?
Me?
Some other day
Sir, should I bring tea?
Now you'll get tea?
Let it be!
You go and get my clothes
from the laundry!
Sir, money!
My wallet is on the table
take it from that!
Okay
Anitaji...
...Whose this?
She's not at home!
She has gone for some party!
I dont know
She'll come late!
Sorry?
I am her wife
Why?
You felt bad?
Greetings
Pushpa!
Come in
After a long inspection I found
sweetness only in 2 places...
...1 where they sell sweets....
...and 2nd is your voice!
I have got sweets for you!
You sit!
I'll serve you in a plate!
No, I dont like eating sweets....
...I just like seeing them!
When you dont eat....
....then why do you get something
everyday!
I have a habit!
I like it!
You like salty food right?
Salty food and spicy food that burns
every thing inside!
Get the bottle
I am getting
Listen!
Get Samosas and Kachoris tomorrow!
You'll eat?
I wont let you have till
you dont eat food!
I'll make something quickly!
Listen
Do you know how to make puris
(bread fried in oil)
Puri?
Potato Vegetable!
Hot pudding
Do you know how to make it?
You'll eat all of this?
Definitely!
If you sit next to me and make
me have!
I'll just get!
Mother has sent clothes for washing!
Keep it here
And these are my father's clothes....
....iron them and send them by tomorrow morning!
Okay
Greetings!
Natwarlalji!
Newspaper is for reading news and
you are hiding your face behind it?
Anand Babu, theres some problem!
Problem?
One Pathan is finding me!
He recoginized me!
I thought you are hiding from me!
We are different sides of
the same coin!
I am totally unashamed of coming
to this place!
I am leaving
What is the hurry?
Anand Babu, those two sweet and innocent
girls...
..they are waiting for you?
Leave
Why did you take so long?
My new mother had sent me
to the washerman!
You'll eat samosas?
I'll heat it?
-Yes
I'll just get it
Have!
Who is he?
He is Nandu
You had met my brother, right?
His eldest son!
He stays opposite us!
He really likes Samosas?
Yes
Take some more
Okay, Now you leave and come
tomorrow
Tomorrow also you'll give
me these?
Yes definitely!
Now go
You really love him!
Anand babu
How many children you have?
I dont have
And wife?
I have one!
She is a very decent woman!
Why do you leave her alone
at home and come here
You are a decent man!
Pushpa
A man can be decent...
....as well as indecent
I come here to see the devil within me!
Do you really come here
for this?
Should I ask you something Pushpa?
You are a defamed woman
Then why does Nandu, a boy
from a decent family, come here?
Thats a different story
He has a step mother...
....she doesnt like him!
No one likes me!
Dont say this
And so I come here
Dont ask me this ever again!
Have water
From where did you get
this samosa from?
From there!
From where?
She stays opposite us!
She gave me
Very bad, punk, shameless,
why did you go there?
Throw it
You eat what she gives?
Useless!
Why, whats wrong with her?
No need for you to
know that!
I'll break your legs if
you again go to her place!
Munni, you stay with him
C'mon Raju
Ashok Kumar has acted so well
in Sanghram!
I am a fan of Dev Anand
I watched Waaji and he came
to my dreams for continuous 3 nights
Dev Anand and Ashok Kumar have become
actors...
.....and the foolish guy who....
....buys a ticket of Balcony...
...he has no value?
You became upset without
any reason
Then what?
You are the real hero!
Natwarlalji...
.....today if you would have
bumped into your wife in the theatre then?
How would I bump into her?
My work is not poor
People like us keep an eye on our wives!
Then what about them?
We see them through glasses!
What about us?
Goggles on you!
The glasses that you wear...
...under the sun that doesnt damage
your eye!
He is caught
Who is caught?
You!
Khan Sir
You have come here to listen
to songs?
Shut up, where is my money?
You'll get it
Meet these girls first
She is Pyaari and she
is Dulhari!
You'll get flattered
seeing their dance!
You have broken my trust!
Its been 3 months....
...I havent got my money
I dont know where were you?
Today I'll take the money and will go!
Very Sorry Khan saab, I cant
pay you today!
You come on Monday...
....we dont give money on Mondays!
Okay, I'll spare you today...
...I'll come to your place
tomorrow in the morning!
Definitely!
If you will not come tomorrow morning,
I'll come to you!
I'll definitely come tomorrow!
And I'll take my money from you
Natwarlalji!
-Yes!
You borrow money from Pathans?
I have to borrow!
We have to borrow money
before coming to your houses!
You joke a lot
Pyaali will you eat Panipuri
(street snack in India)?
Panipuri?
Yes, treat us with panipuri!
Now dont insist so much
I have just showed you'll a movie!
So what?
You like us, isnt it?
I'll like you more if you
cut down your costs!
We'll hardly eat anything
C'mon
Make one plate of panipuri!
Make!
You are only serving them!
Serve me also!
I have to pay money!
Give me! No!
Dont put Tamarind water in it!
I have got water, put this!
I myself will put water
Its Palidhar's water
Give me more
Its over!
Its over? No problem
Even my water is over!
How much?
15 rupees Sir
15 Rupees?
No problem take it
My pocket is torn!
Whether someone has robbed it or
your pocket is torn you will have to pay!
I'll pay you
Do you have anything in your purse?
Its empty
Its empty?
what is your name?
Bindu!
Bindu, take this!
Keep this!
I dont drink!
Who is asking you to drink?
I have kept it on Mortgage!
I'll come tomorrow give you your money
and take this back!
Pushpa
Look I got Kachoris along with
Samosas!
Where is your son?
Are you joking?
Pushpa you are joking!
With yourself!
I should get for you?
No, Later!
Make him have for whom I have
got!
He has still not come?
No
I'll tell mother you are going there!
Mother he is again going!
Nandu, again you are going there!
God knows what has that bitch done to you?
She is totally shameless....
....she even spoils children!
C'mon in!
What are you looking there,
I am fed up!
This child has made my
life miserable!
What happen atleast tell me!
Again you are crying?
How many times have I told you Pushpa...
...I hate tears!
You are running towards darkness!
Your thirst wont quench
and you'll drown!
Whats left in my life now?
Anand Babu wouldnt have existed
if nothing was left in your life!
He wouldnt have given
you money every month!
He wouldnt have beautified you!
Truthfully...
...I had never thought
I'll love Nandu so much!
Like every woman I had dreamt of...
...my own house!
I'll have a husband, children...
But nothing happened!
Nothing came true
Gentleman, arent you ashamed of staying with
your wife in this area?
I have to hide my face and walk from
this area!
You can still hide your face...
...but what should I do?
Because of these women I cant
even leave the house!
Dont worry!
"People will say things"
".....their business is to talk"
"Ignore their useless talks lest the night never end"
"People will say things"
".....their business is to talk"
"Ignore their useless talks lest the night never end"
"People will say things"
"some of the world s tradition is as..."
"..... predictable as the fact that every
morning has an evening"
"some of the world s tradition is as..."
"..... predictable as the fact that every
morning has an evening"
"who are you what s your name...."
".....even sita was slandered here"
"so why do your eyes grow moist....."
".....hearing the their talks"
"People will say things"
".....their business is to talk"
"Ignore their useless talks lest the night never end"
"People will say things"
"Those who taunt us for
being lost in debauchery"
"We ve come secretly and silently and
seen them here in these lanes"
"this is the truth not a false rumor
tell me isn t this the truth"
"People will say things"
".....their business is to talk"
"Ignore their useless talks lest the night never end"
"People will say things"
".....their business is to talk"
No Laxmi, I dont want to stay here
anymore!
Where else will you go?
Where ever you'll go, people
ought to defame you!
I have asked him to find a flat
in a decent area!
Yes, Anand Babu is wealthy...
...if he wants he can buy one!
Excuse me!
Anyone named Pushpa lives here?
I am Pushpa
I want to tell you something
Yes
Here?
Where do you live?
Come
This is my room!
Sit
Anand babu comes here?
Who are you?
He comes or no?
Answer to me!
Please be polite
I dont even know you!
Anand Babu is my brother in law
And my sister doesnt want him
to come here!
Why does your sister allow him
to come here?
Forcibly he comes here!
When your sister cannot stop him...
Look I dont want to argue with you!
Understood?
If my brother in law comes here
please ask him to leave!
What is the use of my refusal?
Can you stop him?
I am not alone in this big
city!
I dont care if you are staying alone
or with somebody!
Just stop him from coming here!
Thats it
I cannot refuse him!
Why dont you tell him you are at a loss!
You dont have a brother or a son!
How will you understand my sister's
sorrow?
You can only see money!
Why are you talking nonsense!
Who are you?
I am Anand Babu's relative!
So why have you come here?
Mind ur language
You mind ur language
You come to my place and
boss over us!
Leave from here
Leave
Aunty what are you doing?
You can leave
I promise you...
...Anand Babu will never come
here back again!
Thank you for that
Pushpa what did you do?
You'll leave Anand Babu just
because he said?
I became strong the day....
.....I had come here!
Then why this foolishness?
Foolishness?
You wont understand that!
Why are you crying?
For you
Why dint you come yesterday?
My father and my new mother,
stop me from coming here!
They say bad people come
to your place!
Now nobody will come!
From today I wont let anyone
come except for you!!
Wont let anyone come!
Pushpa why is this door closed today?
Open the door
Your beloved is standing at the door
please open this closed door!
Why are you taking so long
today?
Open the door
Pushpa!
Go away from here Anand Babu!
I should go away?
Why?
Dont ever come back again!
What has happened to you
all of a sudden?
Atleast open the door
Pushpa
No, you return back
Back to your wife!
You are sending me to the person
I leave and come!
I dont come to go back!
Then you keep standing outside!
You are on the road and
the door is closed?
There is a festival today?
The roads are very crowded and
outside every room there is a que!
Which que are you standing in!
I dont believe in ques!
I believe if one door is closed
enter in the next room!
Thats why I love 2 females!
If Pyaari is not available,
Dulhari is there!
Come!
With you?
Dont worry, I have this with me!
Its Indian!
Anand Babu, sometimes you should
also enjoy Indian one!
Come On!
Hey Anand Babu
Keep your left leg forward!
Left?
Okay
Pyaari, Dulhaari!
Look whose here!
Anand babu, you?
We've been lucky today!
Early morning whose face did we see?
You saw my face, you have
forgotten?
A curse like you!
Come in Anand Babu
Have a seat
Sit!
I got you here and they are serving you!
Sit
Fill 1 to 2 glasses for Anand Babu
and for me!
Anand Babu
Why are you silent?
Why are you sad?
Nothing happen
Dont lie to me, you are sad!
Say
Natwarlalji
What should I tell you?
Tell me what happen?
Should I?
"What happened?"
"How did it happen?"
"When did it happen?"
Now what more?
"What happened?"
"How did it happen?"
"When did it happen?"
"Why did it happen?"
"When it had to happen, it happened"
"let it go don t think about what happened"
"What happened?"
"How did it happen?"
"When did it happen?"
"Why did it happen?"
"When it had to happen, it happened"
"let it go don t think about what happened"
"What happened?"
"Why should I complain...."
".....because of
which broke my heart?"
"Why should I complain...."
".....because of
which broke my heart?"
"It was like a glass"
"Something had to happen"
"What happened?"
"How did it happen?"
"When did it happen?"
"Why did it happen?"
"When it had to happen, it happened"
"let it go don t think about what happened"
"What happened?"
Understood?
"what I had seen and
what I had heard...."
"....how do I explain what it was"
"what I had seen and
what I had heard...."
".....how do I explain what it was"
"It was a beautiful dream it
had to end and it happened"
"What happened?"
"How did it happen?"
"When did it happen?"
"Why did it happen?"
"When it had to happen, it happened"
"What happened?"
"My heart swings after a drink"
"It roams in these lanes"
"You had to loose yourself here
and get defamed"
"What happened?"
"How did it happen?"
"When did it happen?"
"Why did it happen?"
"When it had to happen, it happened"
"let it go don t think about what happened"
"What happened?"
Come in Sir!
What is the time?
Its 2 o clock
Its 2 o clock?
You havent slept as yet?
No Sir, Even madam has not returned
as yet!
When your Sir is tired of waiting...
...then why are you awake, Balraamji?
Hariraamji, Sir!
Younger brother?
Close the door and sleep!
Pushpa dint do any good
by ignoring Anand Babu!
The one who doesnt care about herself,
what is the use talking about her?
Here he comes
Monster!
What are you doing here?
Nothing
Nothing!
Grandson of the Nawab!
He is a waste!
Go
3 days are left for the
pooja (worship)!
The idol is still not complete!
You havent still got the soil
from the singers courtyard!
I dont understand one thing...
.....why is the holy idol of Durga Ma
made with that filt?
Who knows
Its an old tradition!
Without including that soil
the idol is not complete!
You do your work,
I'll get the soil!
When will you color the idol uncle?
In 1 or 2 days!
Where did you get Night jasmine from?
From the garden opposite us!
Go and plant it at home!
Many flowers will blossom!
Really?
-Yes
Then what?
Go and plant it
Else it will dry up!
Go
What will you do with this mud?
The idol of Durga Ma will be made
with this mud!
Is it good?
Good? it is extremly holy!
Can I plant this here?
Yes, why not?
Plant it
Thank you
Greetings
What are you doing?
I am planting.....
.....Night jasmine
When it will grow...
...many flowers will blosoom on it
And what will you do with
those flowers?
I'll pluck a flower
and will give it to you!
Me?
-Yes
You pray to god, right?
You know...
....when this plant will grow,
one bird will....
.....sit on it and make a nest
on it!
Really?
Then what?
Then on the full moon day, the bird's
mother will keep 3 eggs in it!
Very nice, on the full moon day the bird's
Who told you all this?
Lalu!
Who is Lalu?
My friend!
He stays in the village!
Have you ever been to
Madhapur?
Madhavpur?
-Yes
Earlier, We used to stay there!
There was a big nest By the lake,
under the tree
Lalu picked it up....
...placed it on the tree
And said on the full moon day the bird's
mother will keep 3 eggs in it!
Are you listening to me?
I am listening
look, I have planted a sapling here
Dont let it dry
No child
I will never let it dry
Never!
You?
Yes I remember you had refused
me to come here!
Then why did you come?
Why can I not come?
To know that
Your wife doesnt want you to come!
World's any wife wouldnt
want...
.....her husband to come here!
Then why do you upset her?
Happiness, the little happiness
I have got,...
....I have got it here!
My wedding is the biggest question of my life!
Still she is your wife
Yes, this is like a trump card for her!
And so my house is a house of cards
How many ever times I try to make it
...that many times it breaks!
God knows how would she be....
...who is not happy with
a man like you!
Forget about her!
Even you dont want Pushpa...
.....I should forget my
sorrow for sometime!
Anand Babu...
Did you water my plant?
Plant?
Which plant?
Night Jasmine!
He got it from somewhere and
planted it in our courtyard!
The answer that I expected from you
I got it from Nandu Babu
Nandu Babu will blossom flowers
in your courtyard
Night jasmine
I am a hurdle!
Dont say that
There is no harm in telling
the truth!
This plant can dry if I come here
The night jasmine will wither!
No
You dont know!
I have a lot of faith in you!
I like you so much!
You like me?
Yes
And so I dont want you to come here!
If you dont want me to come
I wont come!
May be after today we wont meet....
....but still at anytime you need my
help dont hesitate to ask me!
I am leaving!
Nandu Babu
I am leaving
But before leaving I bless you...
......many flowers will blossom on
your plant!
Many flowers will blossom on
my plant?
Yes
Many flowers will blossom on
your plant!
Your life will bloom...
.....with the fragrance of the plant!
I'll leave
Okay Pushpa
Nandu...
....you are sleeping so
early today?
What happen?
My head is paining father
You have high fever
Hello
Nandu has high fever
Obviously he'll have...
...entire day wanders around
under the sun and wouldnt listen to me!
...now suffer!
Call the doctor and get
medicines for him!
I am not free you can sit
and look after him!
I have a lot of work
Where are you going?
-To the temple!
Pushpa, since a few days havent
seen your son!
Where is he?
I dont know
His parents dont like him
coming here....
....may be they have refused him!
Nandu
You havent come since 2 days!
What happen to you?
High fever
You have fever?
Where is your new mother?
She is sleeping in another room
My sister is awake
If she sees you...
...she'll wake mother!
And new mother will be upset!
You go I'll get well soon and
come to meet you!
No, No get well....
...and then you come!
Have this
Why did you keep down?
I dont like Sago!
Then you'll have sweets in fever?
Are you having it or no?
No
I wont have it
Oh god, was he my enemy
in my last birth?
C'mon come with me!
Let him die
Idiot
Nandu
How are you now?
I still have fever!
Why?
So many days have passed,
the doctor doesnt come?
He comes
Homeopathic doctor!
Homeopathy?
Why havent you called some
good doctor?
They charge a lot
My father doesnt have money!
Look, I have got grapes and apples
for you!
Will you take it?
Yes
Take it
Eat it!
Nandu, whom are you talking to?
Who is there?
No one mother!
You sleep!
Now you go, mother
is awake!
Greetings!
Munimji Greetings!
Anand Babu has sent this letter!
Look tell Anand Babu...
...to meet me once!
Okay
I have some important work!
Try coming this evening
Okay
Brother your head is paining?
Yes Raju
Dont you worry
Doctor Gosh will be there!
Take this
What for?
They are yours
Give it to the doctor
Let me help you for
this little thing!
Keep it
And listen...
....Mahesh shouldnt come to know
That we have sent a doctor
to their place!
I understood!
Pushpa, I knew you are a...
...very nice person!
But you have a big heart,
today I got to know!
I open up everytime
I meet you!
You should consult a
specialist!
Specialist?
Yes
This case is complicating!
Doctor Gosh is the perfect
one to consult!
Doctor Gosh?
-Yes
But his fees is very high, right?
Yes!
He doesnt even lessen a single penny!
Still he is a well known specialist!
Mr. Mahesh
Whose it?
Doctor Gosh
You are Mr. Mahesh
-Yes
Your son is unwell?
Yes!
Hes here?
C'mon!
Show your tongue!
Nandu remove your tongue!
Little more
Thats it
Okay, give me one paper
Take this
What is your child's name?
Nandu
Get this medicine from my dispensary...
...dont worry
Everything will be fine!
Okay doctor
Doctor, your fees?
Dont worry about the fees
First get the medicines
and cure him!
okay I am leaving
I am running late
Okay
Anand you are still here?
I thought of asking you!
Anything serious?
Would have been serious if
you would be late with the treatment!
He has typhoid
Nothing serious right?
Everything will be fine
Dont worry about the expenses
for his treatment
Take 200 rupees rest...!
Why would I take money from you?
I am not giving you this money
but it from the mother!
Okay
Tell me one thing...
How are you related to Nandu?
Relation?
If someone doesnt belong to you and
you still relate to him...
what will you say?
Its a lovely relationship!
You wont understand!
You wont understand
Nandu Babu you are perfectly alright!
From when can I start eating normally?
Wait for two more days you
can eat whatever you want!
Okay
Okay I am leaving okay
Mahesh Babu
-Yes!
Dont change the medicine!
Continue those medicines for
two more days!
Doctor, I'll ask you something
I hope you dont feel bad!
Tell me
You have been visiting us
since so long, you havent taken your fees....
...neither did you charge for
the medicines...
I cant understand a single thing!
But I can understand everything!
What?
You are Bholanath!
Meaning?
His mother has already paid me for the
medicines and my fees in advance
Dont you kow?
Strange
Gentlemen, besides office...
...arent you updated about
your house?
Kamla, I dont understand anything!
Who paid him?
God knows, even I dont understand!
Surprising
Today after returning from office....
.....I'll find out!
Listen...
....now we should fix a date!
I have taken a leave application
It will be approved quickly!
I am going to the village after so long...
...I dont have a saree!
Please buy one sari!
I'll get my pay today,
I'll get from the market!
My Nandu is alright now?
He is completely fine!
Give him Sago to eat
he'll be fine till tomorrow!
Any of your fees is left pending?
No
Tell me one thing, the
fees that you have paid me...
.....why is it that Mahesh Babu is
unaware of it?
The thing is...
....I am not his real mother!
Greetings
Pushpa
Pushpa, listen to me
I did a big mistake in
recognizing you!
You havent just paid for the medicines and
his fees....
...but you have a new life to Nandu
I did not have money for his treatment!
I can never pay you....
...back your favour done to me!
I misunderstood you!
Please forgive me for that!
Brother
Yes sister
Besides Faith and devotion...
....I cannot give you anything!
This is a sari
Remember this brother and wear....
.....it on the Bhai dooj
(festival of brother-sister relation in India)
Aunty!
My son is back?
You are completely fine now?
Isnt it?
Yes
I have bought biscuits for you!
But before that I'll get an amulet
for you!
Wait
Whose is it?
Godess! I had wished....
....that you get well soon!
Keep it tied!
You'll never fall ill!
Is it made out of gold?
You are my gold
My darling son
Wait, I'll get biscuit for you
Nandu
Where did he go?
Nandu, Where did you go?
Nandu
"Krishna is a very mischievous rogue"
"what will his foster-mother
Yashoda do with him?"
"Krishna is a very mischievous rogue"
"what will his foster-mother
Yashoda do with him?"
"He's very naughty!"
"My eyes search for him in all four directions"
"who knows where Krishna has hidden himself?"
"He's flown away like the east wind"
"what will his foster-mother
Yashoda do with him?"
"Mother"
"what will Yashoda-Ma do with him?"
"He is very naughty"
"You are my life's only dream"
"Whoever beholds you considers you beloved."
"You're everyone's darling,
You're everyone's darling"
"player of the flute [i.e., Krishna]."
"what will his foster-mother
Yashoda do with him?"
"Mother"
"Krishna is a very mischievous rogue"
"what will Yashoda-Ma do with him?"
"He's very mischievous!"
You know we are leaving from
here day after tomorrow?
You are going?
Where?
-Village
You'll leave me and go!
Everyone is going even I'll have to go!
You'll never meet me again?
Why not?
I'll come to meet you!
I'll definitely come back
Now I'll go?
Go
Dont remove it!
That cheap woman has tied it
for you!
Worthless, Shameless!
Bindiya!
Take this and give it to Pushpa
and tell that witch...
....her sins are not less!
And now she would tie such amulets
and wants to Witchcraft on children?
Throw it on her face!
Nandu, only 2 days left
to return back to the village!
I'll break your bones if you
again go there!
Understood?
Pushpa
Take this amulet!
Kamla, all packed?
Yes
Even I have packed everything...
...I'll get the car
Nandu Babu
Come in
You got hurt
No problem
I'll apply some cement on it
It will be fine!
No No I'll get medicine!
Nandu
Nandu let it be
Mother, brother has come!
What are you doing?
Where did you go?
What is in your hand? Show me!
Medicine? Who needs it?
Hers
Pushpa
Now you are stealing medicines
and taking for her
Yes I'll go!
Give it to me!
I wont give, leave me!
You are back answering me!
How dare you?
Come back, I will kill you!
What are you doing?
You got medicines for me!
You bandaged me!
So what happen?
What happen?
That you wont understand!
I'll never forget this day
You all are going today?
Yes
In sometime
Father has gone to get the car
You'll never meet me?
Why not?
When I'll grow up...
...I'll come to meet you!
And I'll take my amulet again!
Keep it safely!
Yes
I'll definitely treasure it
Okay I am leaving
Otherwise my new mother will hit
me a lot!
Go!
What is this?
You are touching my feet
inspite being a son of a Brahman!
You love me so much and so
I'll worship you
Go
God bless you always!
Mother, brother has come!
You are back?
Worthless, Shameless!
You went there
You bited me and went to
aid her?
Went to aid her!
She is your mother and I mean
nothing to you
I'll kill you
Give me an answer
My wish, I'll go!
Again you'll go?
Hit me how much ever you want
I'll go!
You are back answering me?
I wont spare you today
Will you go again?
Yes I'll go
You are back answering me?
Dont hit him, he is not at fault!
Hit me how much ever you want
I'll go!
He'll never come to meet me!
I join my hands, please stop it
Dont hit him!
You want to go there,
go die!
Why did you come?
Say? Why did you come?
You were hurt on your leg
Why would you bother if my leg got hurt?
Could have left me to die
Say, you'll never come again
to meet me!
Say
Even you refuse me to come!
I wont come!
No son
How can I stop you?
But what do I do?
Pushpa, go away from here
We are going to leave in sometime!
Before leaving we dont want
to see your face!
"O Mother"
Pushpa, you know your son is
leaving?
I know!
"O Mother"
There are many cars in Calcutta?
-Yes
Many
Cars of 2 floors!
Very big ones!
Really?
And a big variety of food!
What should I tell you?
Samose, Imarti, Kachori!
How do they taste?
Very nice
Everyday your father brought all
this for you?
No
Your new mother would make you have?
She would make me have
Who?
She was very nice
She loved me a lot
Nandu Babu
Dint you recognize me?
Why will you recognize your
villager friend?
Matric failed, Chandar!
Chandar?
Sorry I took time to recognize you
You have completely changed!
In 250 rupees a man stays alive
and should even be well dressed...
...thats not possible!
What do you do?
I am a sales agent of
420 companies!
I sell simulated oil and brushing powder!
Anyway tell me about you!
Heard you are an engineer
Yes I was in Patna for 5 years
and now I am transfered here before a week!
And your parents?
They are still there and I am finding a flat
Okay
How are you here early this morning?
I was passing by from here,
I saw this place and stopped here!
Anything special?
Yes
Look, the dirt of the entire city...
.....from this gutter flow in the
River Ganga
And then this dirt purifies!
Its called Gangajal!
I remembered someone seeing this place!
Whose?
Someone
Her life was like a dirty drain...
...but her soul was pure
like Gangajal!
But who was she?
Not ours
But the affection she gave me....
I think no one would have got
it even from a real mother
I am glad to meet you
Okay I am leaving
I am running late!
I have to sell oil!
I hope we again meet someday!
Find a flat
I'll come to your place for tea
Definitely
Okay
Idiot why are you repeating
so many times!
Mother Ganga is deaf?
I am praying her since 14 years
What has mother Ganga given?
A business of oil between a mob!
And have to scream high!
Poor guy, being a Brahman's son,
he has to sell oil!
Everything depends on luck!
I'll have to see his Horoscope someday!
Brother, read my hand
Today after a great difficulty you've
hold it
I have washed my hands with a soap!
What is this? You used my soap?
Give it to me!
Move aside!
You think fortune telling is magic?
Like you can perform anywhere you want!
Old woman, have you put cotton
in  your ears?
The one in room no 7 is shouting for water!
Go and give him water
I am going!
And these vessels? You havent
still washed them!
These people have to leave for office!
When will I cook?
I dont understand how did my horse loose?
Before that I had won twice!
Leave Shamu,
Our grandparents havent left anything
for us....
....what will their grandparents leave?
Who'll win this time?
Shut up!
What? Has anyone died?
I am sorry,I pushed by mistake!
Put water
Give me water!
Take it!
Ramu
How will I get a kid?
I think I'll die being a bachelor serving you all
day in day out!
Pundari Babu!
Its Pundarikaksh!
I am sorry Pundarikaksh Babu
Where were you since so long?
Ask me where I wasnt present?
I went to buy Rasgulla (Sweet)
for Ghanshaam Babu!
I got tabacco for our chef Jalia!
And for Sitaraam,....
.....I went to polish his shoes!
And for Lal Babu...!
Shut up!
What did I ask you to do?
Every morning you'll fill water!
If I dont get water after I wake up...
....I stomach becomes upset!
Go and get water
I'll just get
Go!
I'll just get!
Give water to him
But this is for the one in room no.7
First he'll have!
Else his stomach becomes upset
Understood?
Greetings! Astrologer, read
my hand and say...
....when will I get married?
You'll get married when you'll pass away!
Punk!
You make fun of my knowledge!
Its 9 already wont we get late?
Even if we get late...!
You?
Here?
I want to ask you this question....
....you and here?
I work here!
Are you fine?
Wrong
You should have asked, are you happy?
Anand, this maid used to work
at your place?
Pushpa, what is this?
You saw me after ages and you started
crying?
You forgot? I hate tears,
wipe those tears!
I have seen many ups and downs
in life!
Thinking that I wont be surprised
with anything!
But today after seeing you I
did get surprised!
This place is better than that place!
Where I lived earlier!
Pushpa!
You wont change whereever you'll
live!
Earlier you cleaned people's
hearts...
....today you clean their utensils!
You purify every particle of dirt just
by touching it!
Do you know...
....you have met me after so
long...
....but I feel I have never stayed
away from you!
C'mon Anand, Chatterji Babu
is waiting for us
Where are you lost?
What is the matter?
Some old realtion with this
maid Pushpa?
You are a broker..
You wont understand!
Sometimes in life.....
....one has to risk.....
......and have to deal with loss!
What?
You wont understand!
C'mon
Ramratan Babu, I am leaving
I have to catch an 8:10 train!
Take care of him
He is ill
Take this
Who are you?
I am a new maid here!
Where is Ramu?
I dont know
I am blind and I am thirsty...
...I cant get water on my own!
Give me!
Sister in law, brother got married
for the second time!
What?
Yes sister in law!
He has got the new bride
home!
Pushpa, take her like younger sister!
And she shouldnt face any problems!
But without telling me?
I dint feel the need
Come
Take this!
You left?
If you meet Ramu, send him here
My head is paining!
Okay I am sending him!
Are you finding something?
Yes
Some years back Durga, Jharna and few more
girls used to stay there
They left long back!
Someone said Jharna passed away
And in that house...
...a girl named Pushpa stayed!
I have no idea about her!
They left long ago!
This house is empty?
Yes, see it
Talk to the watchman!
Thank you
"I would embrace you"
".....no one casts an evil eye on you
and I hide you in my heart"
"I would embrace you"
".....no one casts an evil eye on you
and I hide you in my heart"
"Sun is the world, Affection is shade"
"what will Yashoda-Ma do with him?"
"You are very mischievous"
"You are the only dream of my life"
"Whoever beholds you considers you beloved."
"You are evryone's beloved"
"player of the flute [i.e., Krishna]."
"what will Yashoda-Ma do with him?"
"You are very mischievous"
Get this medicine!
Okay
Later, if needed I'll
give him an injection!
Doctor, your fees?
4 rupees
4 rupees?
I only have 2 rupees
And I even have to renew
the ticket!
I'll pay?
You'll pay?
I have
Listen...
...just inform his reletives!
Reletives?
He has no one!
And so I have got him here
He had 2 wives!
He chucked out the first one!
And the second one committed
suicide!
Take this!
God bless you
You keep these 2 rupees
No
You even have to get his medicines!
Okay, there is milk kept near
the stove...
....heat it and give it to him!
I'll get the medicines and I am
even getting late for office!
No I wont go
Go out from here!
I wont go
I wont leave the house and go
Why wont you?
Either I'll stay in this house
or me!
Its even my house
Its your house? Bitch!
What are you looking at me
Throw her out
Are you going or no?
No, kill me if you want...
....but I wont leave you and
go!
You wont go?
Why wont you go?
Take your clothes and go away
Take this
Samose?
Yes!
Brother in law had got it
You really like it, right?
Very much
Madam, he is crying a lot today!
His body is hot!
He has fever
Yes, dont worry
I'll just get doctor!
Dont worry!
Just little fever!
Give him medicines everything will be fine!
You check and that person doesnt get cured?
You must be not remembering but once
you had treated his father!
When I was 8 years old!
What is your name?
Nand Kishor Sharma!
Nandu
Remembered?
Yes
Now I recollected
After so long?
I used to work in Patna!
I just got transferred to Calcutta!
Okay
What do you do hear?
I am an engineer!
Engineer!
Good
Take this and get these medicines!
Dont worry
Still if you need my help,
do call me!
Yes
Okay Child!
Chef!
What happen?
That man in room no. 7 passed away!
Ramratanji?
Yes
Disaster
Doctor!
-Yes
If you could write a death certificate?
You come with me I'll give you!
"My heart was broken is broken now"
"My bangles splintered just like...."
".....all these dreams into pieces"
"such was the betrayal a gust of wind came"
"and erased the vermilion from the
parting of my hair"
"I was robbed lord ram robbed...."
".....of the sixteen ornaments of traditional beauty"
"Having settled me in the wedding
palanquin the bearer...."
".....carried me on behalf of my beloved"
"Having settled me in the wedding palanquin"
Anand
Come in
Where were you since so
many days?
Sit
Are you fine?
Without falling ill cant I see you?
I felt like meeting all
old friends!
So I dropped in!
I have no complaints!
Neither of body or mind!
I have all the happiness and
peace!
Happiness and peace in this age?
Whats the technique?
Technique?
Simple!
Open up yourself
......and see world's happiness will pour
in like a storm!
Talk about me...
.....earlier, I was not open to anyone!
I used to meet girls....
...I used to drink a lot
And I used to think world's happiness
lies in this!
I was wrong
The day I have opened my heart....
....I stopped everything!
Thats when I found all the happiness
and pleasure!
How can you leave alcohol?
I just left it
Wine, women and even my wife
Even your wife?
Am sorry...
.....sorry my wife left me
It was difficult for her
to live with me
On one hand her husband and
on another hand her parties!
Party, what party?
Anyway
Tell me about yourself
How are you?
I am all fine!
But I had never thought, you
drastically change!
A drastic change in you!
It happens!
No way is straight in life!
There is a turning at every point
You forgot Pushpa?
How?
The one who became a mother
of a child and got him treated from you!
Yes!
That girl opened my mind and soul
Okay
That guy Nandu....
....he is an engineer!
And he stays in this area
Really?
He must have grown up
Actually, his son fell ill...
...and I am doing his treatment
We just remembered you and you are
here!
Come Nandu
Greetings
We just remembered you
You'll live a 100 years
Alone talks wont help.....
....the one who would bless me
I should find her!
Why wont you find her?
I'll bless you
You live thousands of years!
You?
Dint you recognize?
When you were young and
you used to come to Pushpa's place...
....I used to get Samose, sweets and Kachoris!
Remember?
You?
Anand Babu?
Remembered?
Yes
Nandu, again your son has not fallen ill, right?
No
So stop the medicines from today!
Okay
You had planted night jasmine!
Is it still there?
Yes
I am living in the house opposite
that!
Really?
Flowers blossom?
Many
I want to see it
Will you show me?
C'mon
Lets go
Okay doctor!
Anand Babu
Do you know...
...where is she?
She?
Who Pushpa?
You want to see her?
Very much
You want to meet her?
Yes
C'mon
Even you meet her
Okay Doctor I am leaving
What are you doing till now?
Quickly wash it and give it to me!
Pushpa
Pushpa, look who is here
Look
Recognized?
Or I'll have to tell his name!
Nandu
Saw that? You are surprised
seeing her!
But Pushpa recognized you
When had I forgotten him?
Can I ever forget his face?
Pushpa talk to your son I am
just coming!
Come son, we'll sit there!
You have become taller to me!
But you havent changed a bit
Big eyes
The same innocent face
Come son!
Sit
What have you done to yourself?
You are fine?
I had remembered you yesterday
I had cut my finger while
cutting vegetables!
Remember?
I have still kept the...
.....bandage you have tied to me!
1 more thing is with you!
My amulet
Remember?
I had said when I'll grow up...
...I'll come and take it
Yes
I remember!
Will you give me that amulet?
For your grandchild!
My grandchild?
Your son?
Yes
I was going to the temple with him!
And I met you
Wait, I'll just get it
Disaster!
Where did that old woman disappear
leaving these utensils?
Hey old woman, where are you going?
Who'll wash these utensils?
Your father?
Wait, I am doing it
What did you say? Lazy!
I'll find a new maid today
Its a sin to appoint such
cheap women!
Big sin
Take this!
Pushpa!
Look I have got Samose and
Kachori for your son!
Make him have!
Eat
Not only me even he has not
forgotten anything!
Nandu you remember?
In your childhood days, you really
liked it!
Its hot they'll become
cold!
Eat!
Hey you bitch
What are you doing standing there?
Come here and wash utensils
Is he an animal?
Tears in your eyes?
Anand babu!
How do I explain you?
I understaood!
Dont explain me
Wipe your tears I hate tears!
You have washed utensils?
Cant you see?
Look at the dirt!
My finger was cut so..!
Your singer was cut
I'll take it!
If your fingers are so delicate...
....leave from here
Go and dance!
Perform Mujra (form of dance)
Shut up
Who are you to shout here?
Mind your language!
What happen?
Why has everyone gathered here?
I was shouting at the maid but these
people are hurt!
Who are you?
Must be some old friends of
this slut
I'll hit you royally if once
again you say something about her!
Understood?
Now I wont tell her anything!
Sir, why are you siding our maid?
What is so special?
Very much
There is!
Seeing her dont you remember your mother?
Nandu,
This is a chance to pay back
her favours!
Favours?
What favours?
A mother's debt!
Childhood debts
This is the time to take
your mother home...
No
Mother
I wont listen to you
You will have to come along
with me!
Today is Durga Pooja
Today mother Durga goes
to her place!
Today if my mother wont come
along with me...
....I'll understand there is nothing
like love or affection in this world!
But
No buts today!
Your son is taking you home, you go!
C'mon mother
Yes Pushpa!
Rickshaw stop
Nandu sit
Its okay
Live long
What is this?
Tears in your eyes?
Eyes
In my eyes, impossible!
How did they come out
The one who always wiped others
tears...
....theres no one to wipe
his tears?
Let them flow, they have come
out after a great difficulty!
I dint know crying gives you happiness!
Henceforth I'll never say Pushpa I hate
tears!
Seriously you got nothing
from life!
You dint take anything from
anyone!
You just kept giving
Kept spending everything!
Okay Pushpa, your son is
waiting for you!
I am going
I have got a lot
of things from you!
But I couldnt give you anything
And today...
....while going I am taking
something!
The soil underneath your
feet
As and when you reach home
look at night jasmine plant...
Many flowers have blosoomed!
Nandu, take your mother
Richshaw leave
"O Mother"